Guide to the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Oral History Collection, 1981-2014 RL.11031
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Greensboro and surrounding areas, 1998-2008; 6
  - Swartzberg, Fred (High Point), 2004; 154
    - Fred Swartzberg. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2004 July 11; transcript (Box 8, Folder 30)
      "
  - Tannenbaum, Leah, 2002; 155
    - Leah Tannenbaum. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 April; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-003)
      Container label: "Leah Tannenbaum"
    - Leah Tannenbaum. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 April; betacam-sp (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Bcam-004)
    - Leah Tannenbaum. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 April; transcript (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Leah Tannenbaum. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2002 April? (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-VHS-001)
      No audio. The recording was probably transferred from the digital betacam recordings of Tannenbaum's April 2002 interview. Container label: "Leah Tannenbaum"
  - Weil, Charles L. "Buddy", 2005; 156
    - Charles L. "Buddy" Weil. Interviewed by Sandra Sokoloff for Down Home project, 2005 July 20; transcript (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Raleigh, 2006-2007; 7
  - Ehrlich, Alice Rubenstein, 2007; 157
    - Alice Rubenstein Ehrlich. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 7; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-002)
      Container label: "Alice Ehrlich"
    - Alice Rubenstein Ehrlich. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 7; transcript (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Glass, David, 2007; 158
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; audiocassette, 1 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-015)
      Container label: "Glass Horowitz"
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; audiocassette, 2 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-040)
      Container label: "Glass-Hurwitz"
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; audiocassette, 3 of 3 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-086)
      Container label: "Glass/Hurwitz"
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; transcript (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Holtzman, Abe and Sylvia, 2007; 159
    - Abe and Sylvia Holtzman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 August 30; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-134)
      Container label: "Abe Holztman, Side B - Marilyn Farber"
  - Horwitz, Burton, 2007; 160
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; audiocassette, 1 of 3 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-015)
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; audiocassette, 2 of 3 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-040)
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; audiocassette, 3 of 3 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-086)
    - David Glass and Burton Horwitz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 September 8; transcript (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Levine, Leah, 2006; 161
    - Leah Levine. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 May 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-005)
      Container label: "End of Muriel Offerman interview Wallace, NC. Leah Levine interview, Raleigh, NC"
    - Leah Levine. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 May 1; transcript (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Litwack, Charlotte, 2007; 162
    - Charlotte Litwack. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 27; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-007)
      Container label: "Charlotte Litwack"
    - Charlotte Litwack. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 27; transcript (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Pensler, Frances, 2006; 163
    - Frances Pensler. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 December 4; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-009)
      Container label: "Frances Penslar"
  - Satisky, Dan and Alice, 2006; 164
    - Dan and Alice Satisky. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 May 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-007)
      Container label: "Dan and Alice Satisky"
    - Dan and Alice Satisky. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 May 1; transcript (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Weldon and surrounding areas, 1995-2007; undated; 8
  Geographic locations represented in this series include Enfield, Roanoke Rapids, Warrenton, and Weldon, North Carolina, and Emporia, Virginia.
  - Bloom, Betty, 2005; 165
    - Betty Bloom. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 July 12; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-064)
      Container label: "Betty Bloom"
    - Betty Bloom. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 July 12; transcript (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Britton, Brenda, circa 2005; 166
    - Brenda Britton. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2005-2006; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-128)
      Container label: "Brenda Britton"
  - Coblenz, Danny, 2006; 167
    - Danny Coblenz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 August 1; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-121)
      Container label: "Josephson Family/Coblenz/Packer"
  - Cohen, Laverne, 2006; 168
    - Laverne Cohen. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 May 9; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-122)
      Container label: "Laverne Cohen"
    - Laverne Cohen. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 May 9; transcript (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Diamond, Ruth Perman (Warrenton), 2006; 169
    - Ruth Perman Diamond. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 May 22; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-119)
      Container label: "Ruth Diamond"
    - Ruth Perman Diamond. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 May 22; transcript (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Ruth Perman Diamond. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-014)
      Container label: "Warrenton: Elsie Weldon, Ruth Diamond, Hazel Hargrove, Alex and Charles Kazenstein, Bill Frazier; Wilmington Cemetary, Ben D'Lugin"
  - Dickman, Stan and Harriet Bloom, 2005; 170
    - Stan and Harriet Bloom Dickman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 July 11; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-120)
      Container label: "Stan & Harriet Bloom Dickman"
    - Stan and Harriet Bloom Dickman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 July 11; transcript (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Farber, Maralyn, 2006; 171
    - Maralyn Farber. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 April 25; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-156)
      Container label: "Maralyn Farber (alone)"
    - Maralyn Farber. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 April 25; transcript (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Farber, Mark, 2006; 172
    - Mark Farber. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 April 23; notes (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Farber, Morton, 2006; 173
    - Morton Farber. Interview by Maralyn Farber for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 April 25; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-112)
      Container label: "Tape 1, 1) Wildacres experience, Mar. Farber 2) Interview w/Daddy"
    - Morton Farber. Interview by Maralyn Farber for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 April 25; transcript (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Farber, Susan Bloom, 2006; 174
    - Susan Bloom Farber. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 April 26; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-110)
      Container label: "Sarah [Susan] Bloom Farber"
    - Susan Bloom Farber. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 April 26; transcript (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Fox, Jack (Weldon / Emporia, VA), 2006; 175
    - Jack Fox. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 August 3; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-126)
      Container label: "Jack Fox - Weldon"
    - Jack Fox. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 August 3; transcript (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Frazier, Bill (Warrenton), 2007; 176
    - Bill Frazier. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-014)
  - Freid, Harry, circa 2005-2006; 177
    - Harry Freid. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2005-2006; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-130)
      Container label: "Harry Freid"
    - Harry Freid. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2005-2006; transcript (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Green, Lyn Szabo, 2006; 178
    - Lyn Szabo Green. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 August 14; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-041)
      Container label: "Lyn Green"
    - Lyn Szabo Green. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 August 14; transcript (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Hargrove, Hazel (Warrenton), 2007; 179
    - Hazel Hargrove. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-014)
  - Joseph, Hilde (Enfield), circa 1998; 180
    - Hilde Joseph. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-135)
      Container label: "Side B - Hilda [Hilde] Joseph, Side A- Simon & Fanny Habowsky Meyer"
  - Josephson, Anne, 2006; 181
    - Josephson family member [Anne?] interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006?; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-121)
    - Anne Josephson. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2006; notes (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Katzenstein, Alex (Warrenton), 2006-2007; 182
    - Alex Katzenstein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-014)
    - Alex Katzenstein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 March 08?; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-154)
      Container label: "Katzenstein"
  - Katzenstein, Charles (Warrenton), 2007; 183
    - Charles Katzenstein. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-014)
  - Kinghoff, Janice Specter, 2006; 184
    - Janice Specter Kinghoff. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 March 6; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-153)
      Container label: "Janice Specter Kinghoff"
    - Janice Specter Kinghoff. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 March 6; transcript (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Kittner, Ben, 2006; 185
    - Ben Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 17; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-143)
      Container label: "Ben Kittner, Side B - Rhoda Kittner"
    - Ben Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 17; transcript (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kittner, Bert, 2006; 186
    - Bert Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 18; transcript (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kittner, Bill and Ida, 2005; 187
    - Bill and Ida Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 November 7; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-148)
      Container label: "Bill & Ida Kittner"
    - Bill and Ida Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 November 7; transcript (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kittner, Dorothy, circa 2005-2006; 188
    - Dorothy Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2005-2006; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-083)
      Container label: "Dorothy Kittner"
  - Kittner, Harry, 1997; 189
    - Harry Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, 1997 September 8; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-141)
      Container label: "Harry Kittner"
    - Harry Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, 1997 September 8; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kittner, Joseph, 2006; 190
    - Joseph Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 February 2; transcript (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kittner, Rhoda, 2006; 191
    - Rhoda Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 18; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-143)
    - Rhoda Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 18; transcript (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Kittner, Sam, 2006; 192
    - Sam Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 February 2; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-066)
      Container label: "Ben Marks (Side A), Jodi Kittner Laibstain/Sam Kittner (Side B)"
    - Sam Kittner. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 February 2; transcript (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Laibstain, Jody Kittner, 2006; 193
    - Jody Kittner Laibstain. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 14; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-066)
    - Jody Kittner Laibstain. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 14; transcript (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Latham, Lisa Kittner, circa 2005-2006; 194
    - Lisa Kittner Latham. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2005-2006; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-082)
      Container label: "Lisa Kittner Latham"
  - Leinwand, Helen, circa 2005-2006; 195
    - Helen Leinwand. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2005-2006; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-067)
      Container label: "Helen Leiwand"
  - Liverman, Robert (Roanoke Rapids / Weldon), 2005; 196
    - Robert Liverman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 September 15; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-093)
      Container label: "Bob Liverman"
    - Robert Liverman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 September 15; transcript (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Marks, Ben (Roanoke Rapids / Weldon), 2006; 197
    - Ben Marks. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 8; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-066)
    - Ben Marks. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 8; transcript (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Marks, Nancy Liverman (Roanoke Rapids / Weldon), 2006; 198
    - Nancy Liverman Marks. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 5; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-011)
      Container label: "Nancy Marks"
    - Nancy Liverman Marks. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 6; transcript (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - McCabe, Diane Bloom, 2006; 199
    - Diane Bloom McCabe. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 10; detailed summary (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Meyer, Fanny Hobowsky and Simon (Enfield), circa 1998; 200
    - Fanny Hobowsky Meyer and Simon Meyer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-135)
      Container label: "Side B - Hilda Joseph, Side A- Simon & Fanny Habowsky Meyer"
    - Fanny Hobowsky Meyer and Simon Meyer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, circa 1998; index (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Moritz, Betty Liverman (Roanoke Rapids / Weldon), 2006; 201
    - Betty Liverman Moritz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 September 6; transcript (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Novey, Bari (Emporia, VA), 2005; 202
    - Bari Novey. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 July 25; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-080)
      Container label: "Bari Novey"
    - Bari Novey. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2005 July 25; transcript (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Packer, Betty, 2006; 203
    - Betty Packer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 August 1; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-121)
    - Betty Packer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 August 1; transcript (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Powe, Lucia Peel (Weldon / Roanoake Rapids), 2006; 204
    - Lucia Peel Powe. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 November 6; audiocassette (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-004)
      Container label: "Lucia Peel Powe"
  - Scheinerman, Amy, Rabbi, 2006; 205
    - Rabbi Amy Scheinerman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 December 9; transcript (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Szabo, Shirley, 2006; 206
    - Shirley Szabo. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 May 26; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-075)
      Container label: "Shirley Szabo"
    - Shirley Szabo. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 May 26; transcript (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Vatz, Isabelle Freid, circa 2005-2006; 207
    - Isabelle Freid Vatz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, circa 2005-2006; audiocassette (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-145)
      Container label: "Isabel [Isabelle] Vatz"
  - Winer, Marion Silvester, 2006; 208
    - Marion Silvester Winer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 May 10; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-114)
      Container label: "Marion Winer Silvester [Marion Silvester Winer]"
    - Marion Silvester Winer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, NC project, 2006 May 10; transcript (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Weldon, Elsie, 2007; 209
    - Elsie Weldon. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 1; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-014)
- Wilmington and surrounding areas, 1995-2007; undated; 9
  Geographic locations represented in this series include New Bern, Wallace, and Wilmington, North Carolina.
  - Bear, Sigmund, 2005; 210
    - Sigmund Bear. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 February 24; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-044)
      Container label: "Sigmund Bear"
    - Sigmund Bear. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 February 24; transcript (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Sigmund Bear. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 February 24; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-055)
  - Friedman, Miriam, 2005; 211
    - Miriam Friedman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 February 24; audiocassette (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-132)
      Container label: "Miriam Freedman [Friedman]"
  - Block, Hannah, 2005; 212
    - Hannah Block. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 February 25; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-001)
      Container label: "NC Jewish Project 2/25/05 Hannah Block - Piano, intv"
    - Hannah Block. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2005 February 25; transcript (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - D'Lugin, Ben, 2007; 213
    - Ben D'Lugin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 4; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-014)
    - Ben D'Lugin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 4; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-015)
      Container label: "Wilmington: Ben D'Lugin, Miriam Warschauer [Warshauer], Sam Warschauer [Warshauer], Temple of Israel, Old Cemetary Gate"
    - Ben D'Lugin. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 4; transcript (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Kramer, Vivian (Wilmington / Wallace), 2006; 214
    - Vivian Kramer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 April 7; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-004)
      Container label: "Vivian Kramer/Muriel Offerman"
  - Kramer, Vivian (Wilmington / Wallace), 2006; 215
    - Vivian Kramer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 April 7; transcript (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Lipman, Elbert (New Bern), 1995; 216
    - Elbert Lipman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, 1995 August 12; audiocassette (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-093)
      Container label: "Elbert Lipman"
    - Elbert Lipman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Migrations project, 1995 August 12; transcript (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Offerman, Muriel (Wallace), 2006; 217
    - Muriel Offerman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 April 7; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-004)
    - Muriel Offerman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 April 7; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-005)
    - Muriel Offerman. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2006 April 7; transcript (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Schwartz, Nathan, 2007; 218
    - Nathan Schwartz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 4; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-016)
    - Nathan Schwartz. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff and Lue Simopolous for Down Home project, 2007 June 15; transcript (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Shain, Art (Wilmington / Chapel Hill), undated; 219
    - Art Shain. Interviewed by unknown interviewer, undated; audiocassette (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL11031-CS-052)
      Container label: "Art Shain Side 1, Poor sound quality"
    - Art Shain. Interviewed by unknown interviewer, undated; index (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Warshauer, Miriam, 2007; 220
    - Miriam Warshauer. Interviewed by Leonard Rogoff for Down Home project, 2007 June 4; digital betacam (Box 6, Video-cassette RL11031-Dbcam-015)